http://www.buckmasters.com/contact/privacy-policy

You are here: Privacy Policy
Buckmasters is a general audience web site, and does not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from children under 13 years of age. COLLECTION: COLLECTION OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION BY BUCKMASTERS General. BUCKMASTERS collects personally identifiable information (that is, information such as your full name, email address, mailing address or telephone number) only in order to create or enhance our relationship with you. When we collect Personally Identifiable Information from you, it is because you voluntarily submit the information to us in order to participate in activities like sweepstakes, contests, games, surveys, forums, subscription registrations, chats or bulletin boards, in connection with content or suggestions you submit to us or because you want us to furnish you with products, services or information. BUCKMASTERS website may be linked to websites operated by other companies. Some of these third party sites may be co-branded with a BUCKMASTERS logo, even though they are not operated or maintained by BUCKMASTERS. BUCKMASTERS website may also carry advertisements from other companies. BUCKMASTERS is not responsible for the privacy practices of web sites operated by third parties that are linked to our site or for the privacy practices of third party or national Internet advertising companies. Once you¹ve left a BUCKMASTERS site via such a link or by clicking on an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party or advertiser site to determine how they will handle any Personally Identifiable Information they collect from you. Some of the advertisements that appear on BUCKMASTERS website are delivered to you by national Internet advertising.CHOICE: BUCKMASTERS Will Provide You with Choices About the Use of Your Personally Identifiable Information BUCKMASTERS will not use the you provide to us for purposes different from the purpose for which it was submitted or share your Personally Identifiable Information with third parties that are not affiliated with BUCKMASTERS, unless we obtain your permission. USE: BUCKMASTERS's Use of PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION BUCKMASTERS will use your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION provided under this Policy in a manner that is consistent with this Policy. If BUCKMASTERS obtains PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION from a third party, such as a business partner, our use of that information is governed by this Policy. BUCKMASTERS employees, agents and contractors must have a legitimate business reason to obtain access to your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION. BUCKMASTERS may share your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION with outside contractors or agents who help us manage our information activities (sweepstakes administration, order fulfillment, statistical analyses) but they may only use your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION to provide BUCKMASTERS with a specific service and not for any other purpose. BUCKMASTERS may also enter into agreements with outside companies that possess the technology that allows BUCKMASTERS to customize the advertising and marketing messages you receive on our web sites. Your non-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION and click stream data about your activities on our sites may be shared with these companies so this customization can be accomplished. These companies will not share your information with any third party or use it for any other purposes. Anonymous click stream and demographic information may also be shared with BUCKMASTERS¹s advertisers and business partners. There may be instances when BUCKMASTERS may disclose PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION without providing you with a choice in order to protect the legal rights of BUCKMASTERS; to protect the safety and security of visitors to our web sites; to protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or to comply with the law or legal process. In addition, if BUCKMASTERS sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, BUCKMASTERS may transfer your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION to a third party as part of that transaction. SECURITY: BUCKMASTERS Protects the Security of PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION BUCKMASTERS uses reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. In addition, BUCKMASTERS uses reasonable methods to make sure that PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION is accurate, up-to-date and appropriately complete.
Facebook Twitter
Big Buck Central
Gear For Deer
Outfitters
Tips & Tactics
Ask The Biologist
Available in our Online Store
Buckmasters1 Year Membership$19.95
Buckmasters entertains and educates deer hunters with current strategies and technology from the most respected experts in the field.
Copyright 2020 by Buckmasters, Ltd.
